const anatomySeed = [
  {
    category: "63960b51cd6b86a544c3a509",
    question: 'What is the phospholipid bilayer with embedded protiens that surrounds every cell?',
    correctAnswer: 'Cell membrane',
    incorrectAnswers: [
      {
        1: 'Cell wall',
        2: 'Cholesterol',
        3: 'Osmosis'
      }]
  },
  {
    category: "63960b51cd6b86a544c3a509",
    question: 'What is the medical term for a bone cell?',
    correctAnswer: 'Oocyte',
    incorrectAnswers: [
      {
        1: 'Myocyte',
        2: 'Neuron',
        3: 'Steriod'
      }]
  },
  {
    category: "63960b51cd6b86a544c3a509",
    question: 'What is the term for the support cells in the Nervous System (i.e.: Oligodendrocytes and Astrocytes?',
    correctAnswer: 'Neuroglial Cells',
    incorrectAnswers: [
      {
        1: 'Oocyte',
        2: 'Neuron',
        3: 'Myocyte'
      }]
  },
  {
    category: "63960b51cd6b86a544c3a509",
    question: 'What is the medical term for the sense of smell?',
    correctAnswer: 'Olfaction',
    incorrectAnswers: [
      {
        1: 'Stank',
        2: 'Gustation',
        3: 'Canudu'
      }]
  },
  {
    category: "63960b51cd6b86a544c3a509",
    question: 'What is the medical term for the sense of taste?',
    correctAnswer: 'Gustation',
    incorrectAnswers: [
      {
        1: 'Sphincter',
        2: 'Olfaction',
        3: 'Yummy'
      }]
  },
  {
    category: "63960b51cd6b86a544c3a509",
    question: 'What is the structure at the back of the eye that contains the rod and cone cells?',
    correctAnswer: 'Retina',
    incorrectAnswers: [
      {
        1: 'Lens',
        2: 'Pupil',
        3: 'Soft palate'
      }]
  },
  {
    category: "63960b51cd6b86a544c3a509",
    question: 'What is the structure of the eye that supplies blood and gives our eyes color?',
    correctAnswer: 'Iris',
    incorrectAnswers: [
      {
        1: 'Lens',
        2: 'Pupil',
        3: 'Retina'
      }]
  },
  {
    category: "63960b51cd6b86a544c3a509",
    question: 'What is the hole through which light passes into the eye?',
    correctAnswer: 'Pupil',
    incorrectAnswers: [
      {
        1: 'Cell Membrane',
        2: 'Sphincter',
        3: 'Retina'
      }]
  },
  {
    category: "63960b51cd6b86a544c3a509",
    question: 'What are the visible bumbs on the surface of the tongue that each contain many taste buds?',
    correctAnswer: 'Papillae',
    incorrectAnswers: [
      'Taste Buds',
      'Soft Palete',
      'Hard Palete'
    ]
  },
  {
    category: "63960b51cd6b86a544c3a509",
    question: 'What is the anatomical term for situated nearer to the center of the body or the point of attachment ("closer to")?',
    correctAnswer: 'Proximal',
    incorrectAnswers: [
      {
        1: 'Distal',
        2: 'Superior',
        3: 'Inferior'
      }]
  },
  {
    category: "63960b51cd6b86a544c3a509",
    question: 'What are chemical messengers that are released into the bloodstream (Hint: Target cells only respond to them if they have receptors specific to them)?',
    correctAnswer: 'Hormones',
    incorrectAnswers: [{
      1: 'Neurons',
      2: 'Pheromones',
      3: 'Proteins'
    }]
  },
  {
    category: "63960b51cd6b86a544c3a509",
    question: 'What is conscious interpretation of the external world created by patterns of activity in the brain?',
    correctAnswer: 'Perception',
    incorrectAnswers: [
      {
        1: 'Deception',
        2: 'Attention',
        3: 'Sensation'
      }]
  },
  {
    category: "63960b51cd6b86a544c3a509",
    question: 'What do photorecerptors respond to?',
    correctAnswer: 'Wavelengths of light',
    incorrectAnswers: [
      {
        1: 'Instagram likes',
        2: 'Sounds',
        3: 'Pressure'
      }]
  },
  {
    category: "63960b51cd6b86a544c3a509",
    question: 'What are the 3 tiny bones that transmit vibrations from the tympanic membrane to the cochlea?',
    correctAnswer: 'Auditory Ossicles (malleus, incus, and stapes)',
    incorrectAnswers: [
      {
        1: 'Metallica, Incubus, and Staples',
        2: 'Triumphvirate',
        3: 'Femur, Patella, and Tibia'
      }]
  },
  {
    category: "63960b51cd6b86a544c3a509",
    question: 'What is the property of muscle tissue that refers to the fact that it will return to its normal resting state without being damaged?',
    correctAnswer: 'Elasticity',
    incorrectAnswers: [
      {
        1: 'Excitability',
        2: 'Conductivity',
        3: 'Contractility'
      }]
  },
  {
    category: "63960b51cd6b86a544c3a509",
    question: 'What is the property of muscle tissue that refers to the fact that it will respond to electrical signals?',
    correctAnswer: 'Excitability',
    incorrectAnswers: [
      {
        1: 'Elasticity',
        2: 'Conductivity',
        3: 'Contractility'
      }]
  },
  {
    category: "63960b51cd6b86a544c3a509",
    question: 'What are the building blocks of proteins?',
    correctAnswer: 'Amino acids',
    incorrectAnswers: [
      {
        1: 'Whey',
        2: 'Neurons',
        3: 'Steriods'
      }]
  },
  {
    category: "63960b51cd6b86a544c3a509",
    question: 'What is the medical term for a muscle cell also known as a muscle fiber?',
    correctAnswer: 'Myocyte',
    incorrectAnswers: [
      {
        1: 'Oocyte',
        2: 'Neuron',
        3: 'Steriod'
      }]
  },
  {
    category: "63960b51cd6b86a544c3a509",
    question: 'What is the medical term for a muscle cell also known as a muscle fiber?',
    correctAnswer: 'Myocyte',
    incorrectAnswers: [
      {
        1: 'Oocyte',
        2: 'Neuron',
        3: 'Steriod'
      }]
  },
  {
    category: "63960b51cd6b86a544c3a509",
    question: 'What is a disease characterized by uncontrolled cell division?',
    correctAnswer: 'Cancer',
    incorrectAnswers: [
      {
        1: 'Meiosis',
        2: 'Mitosis',
        3: 'Anemia'
      }]
  },
  {
    category: "63960b51cd6b86a544c3a509",
    question: 'What is a disease characterized by an inability to produce enough insulin to regulate blood glucose levels?',
    correctAnswer: 'Diabetes Mellitus',
    incorrectAnswers: [
      {
        1: 'Juandice',
        2: 'Anemia',
        3: 'Cancer'
      }]
  },
  {
    category: "63960b51cd6b86a544c3a509",
    question: 'What is the outer portion of an organ called, for example the outer portion of a lymph node?',
    correctAnswer: 'Cortex',
    incorrectAnswers: [
      {
        1: 'Medulla',
        2: 'Exterior',
        3: 'Distal'
      }]
  },
  {
    category: "63960b51cd6b86a544c3a509",
    question: 'What is the transparent tissue over the anterior of the eye?',
    correctAnswer: 'Cornea',
    incorrectAnswers: [
      {
        1: 'Retina',
        2: 'Pupil',
        3: 'Lacrima'
      }]
  },
  {
    category: "63960b51cd6b86a544c3a509",
    question: 'What is the snail shaped structure in the inner ear containing hair cells?',
    correctAnswer: 'Cochlea',
    incorrectAnswers: [
      {
        1: 'Auditory Ossicles',
        2: 'Tympanic Membrane',
        3: 'Coccyx'
      }]
  },
  {
    category: "63960b51cd6b86a544c3a509",
    question: 'What is the first segment of the small intestine, located between the pyloric valve of the stomach and the jejunum?',
    correctAnswer: 'Duodenum',
    incorrectAnswers: [
      {
        1: 'Coccyx',
        2: 'Epigolittis',
        3: 'Sphincter'
      }]
  },
  {
    category: "63960b51cd6b86a544c3a509",
    question: 'What are the branches of a neuron that collect stimuli and transport them to the cell body?',
    correctAnswer: 'Dendrites',
    incorrectAnswers: [
      {
        1: 'Axons',
        2: 'Neurotransmitters',
        3: 'Cones'
      }]
  },
  {
    category: "63960b51cd6b86a544c3a509",
    question: 'What is the innermost layer of the heart, which lines the interior of the heart chambers aand covers the valves',
    correctAnswer: 'Endocardium',
    incorrectAnswers: [
      {
        1: 'Ventricle',
        2: 'Atrium',
        3: 'Myocardium'
      }]
  },
  {
    category: "63960b51cd6b86a544c3a509",
    question: 'What is a condition characterized by a decrease in the number of red blood cells or an insufficent amount of hemoglogin?',
    correctAnswer: 'Anemia',
    incorrectAnswers: [
      {
        1: 'Juandice',
        2: 'Crips',
        3: 'Cancer'
      }]
  },
  {
    category: "63960b51cd6b86a544c3a509",
    question: 'What is an essential molecule of the red blood cell that serves as a binding site for oxygen and carbon dioxide?',
    correctAnswer: 'Hemoglobin',
    incorrectAnswers: [
      {
        1: 'Hemacrit',
        2: 'Insulin',
        3: 'Hypoxemia'
      }]
  },
  {
    category: "63960b51cd6b86a544c3a509",
    question: 'What is the triangular-shaped space inferior to the pharynx that is responsible for voice production?',
    correctAnswer: 'Larynx',
    incorrectAnswers: [
      {
        1: 'Trachea',
        2: 'Esophogus',
        3: 'Throat'
      }]
  },
]

module.exports = anatomySeed 